[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":41390,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":48265,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</ sub>, yo u start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":6369,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":54636,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1355,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":55992,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":5518,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":61511,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1230,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":62742,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3825,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":66567,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1268,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":67836,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4321,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":72157,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1185,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":73342,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bi gger, yo u subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":7695,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":81037,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":906,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":81944,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["0","2"],"rt":4595,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":86539,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1073,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":87612,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3017,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":90631,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1351,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":91982,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform + <sub>6</ sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2537,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":94519,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":995,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":95514,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2388,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":97902,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":969,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":98871,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2413,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":101284,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":843,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":102127,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":10887,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":113017,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its o wn inver se under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":28628,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":141646,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":10100,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":151747,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1079,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":152827,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the  thing w hich you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3052,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":155879,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":923,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":156802,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3587,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":160389,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The i nverse o f 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":914,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":161303,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2302,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":163605,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":906,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":164511,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, t he inver se of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2414,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":166925,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":5439,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":172365,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":24909,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":197274,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last de finition  to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":22217,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":219503,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other e lement.) ","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":6873,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":226377,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1907,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":228285,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2246,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":230531,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +< sub>6</s ub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":5646,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":236177,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4965,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":241143,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4  +<sub>6 </sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":6581,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":247725,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3344,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":251069,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1396,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":252465,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4,  5, 6, 7,  8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":9395,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":261861,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3438,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":265299,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1040,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":266339,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4251,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":270590,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3199,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":273789,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2229,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":276019,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2224,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":278243,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2222,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":280465,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5  4+1=5 which is less than 9 so no need to subtract","response_history":["2","5  4+1+","5  4+1=5 which is less than 9 so no need to subtract"],"rt":29395,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":309861,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3  8+4=12 minus 9 because its greater than 9","response_history":["3  8+4=12 minus 9 becaue","3  8+4=12 minus 9 becau","3  8+4=12 minus 9 because its greater tahn ","3  8+4=12 minus 9 because its greater tahn","3  8+4=12 minus 9 because its greater tah","3  8+4=12 minus 9 because its greater ta","3  8+4=12 minus 9 because its greater than 9"],"rt":24806,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":334668,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0  Im not sure","response_history":["0  Im nit","0  Im ni","0  Im n","0  Im not sure"],"rt":15090,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":349759,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4  because 5+4=9","response_history":["4  beacuse 5+4=9","4  because 5+4=9"],"rt":14388,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":364147,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":4534,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":368681,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 6+3=9","response_history":["6 6+3=9"],"rt":8554,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":377235,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes because you can get all the numbers","response_history":["no becase","yes becasue you an","yes becasue you a","yes becasue you can get all the numbers","yes because you can get all the numbers"],"rt":78019,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":455254,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes because you can get all the numbers","response_history":["yes becaue yo ","yes becaue yo","yes becaue y","yes becaue ","yes becaue","yes becau","yes because you can get all the numbers"],"rt":31716,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":486971,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because you cant get all the nmbers","response_history":["no becasue you cant get al the nmbers","no becasue you cant get all the nmbers","no because you cant get all the nmbers"],"rt":12480,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":499451,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes because you can get all the numbers","response_history":["yrr","yr","yes becasue yo ","yes becasue you can get all the numbers","yes because you can get all the numbers"],"rt":12151,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":511602,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other cou nting nu mber you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":5967,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":517569,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"not sure","response_history":["not sure"],"rt":14450,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":532019,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"dont know","response_history":["dont know"],"rt":11502,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":543521,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"??","response_history":["??/","??"],"rt":7922,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":551443,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4799,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":556243,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"Fal se","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4202,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":560445,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":5807,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":566253,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"yes, because it must be a multiple","response_history":["yes, because it must be a multiple"],"rt":18028,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":584281,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0 .13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","response_history":["Always"],"rt":14275,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":598556,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"always, it remains the same","response_history":["always, it reamins the same","always, it remains the same"],"rt":19842,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":618399,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a ge nerator  under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Never","Sometimes"],"rt":32310,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":650709,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1803,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":652513,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"42","response_history":["42"],"rt":5068,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":657581,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":3074,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":660655,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"geometry","response_history":["geometyr","geomety","geomet","geome","geometry"],"rt":18735,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":679391,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3832,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":683223,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3026,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":686249,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learne d someth ing from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3056,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":689306,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2577,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":691883,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2885,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":694771,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":3034,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":697805,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"english","response_history":["english"],"rt":5203,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":703009,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no I did not","response_history":["no I didn","no I did not"],"rt":6370,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":709379,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"the language was a bit confusing.","response_history":["it ","it","i","the languauge ","the languauge=","the languauge","the languaug","the languau","the langua","the language was a bit confusing."],"rt":14757,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":724136,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]